https://theaamgroup.com/privacy

Date of Last Revision: August 20, 2020
You take your privacy seriously, and so do we. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe what types of information we gather about our users as well as how we use it. You'll also learn about what you can do to learn about or opt out of the data we collect (such information will be indicated in bold throughout this Privacy Policy). This Privacy Policy applies to the website located at www.theaamgroup.com as well as any related websites or apps (mobile or desktop). Hereafter, this collection of related assets will be referred to as the "Site."
Our digital infrastructure automatically captures no data pertaining to the domains or email addresses of our users except for data gathered through Google Analytics. We do collect the email addresses of users who communicate with us through email, but these are used only as they relate to our own internal evaluations.
If you do not wish to receive future emails from us, notify us of your preference by emailing us at the address listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.
We may collect information about you—such as your name and contact information—when you interact with our Site in certain ways (e.g., by making purchases or subscribing to email lists).
This information may be shared with affiliates who are controlled by, who control, or who are under common control with the The AAM Group™.
We may share this information, along with a record of any transactions you conduct on our Site or with us offline, with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver interest-specific advertising to you when you visit certain other websites. Data shared with third-party partners remain anonymous.
Additionally, we may enlist the services of third parties to deliver services and marketing to you not limited to processing payments and orders or designing custom sites for your use. If personally identifiable information must be provided to any of these third parties, we will require that it be held to privacy standards that at least meet those outlined in this Privacy Policy.
We employ cookies to allow our customers to log in to their accounts. We may create and implement additional cookies in order to provide you with online advertising tailored to your interests.
We may direct you to third-party websites or suggest that you download a third-party application. Any such recommendation is presented for your convenience only; it does not signify our endorsement of the third party or its products or services. Clicking on such a link or downloading such an application will cause you to leave our Site. As part of this process, the third party may collect personally identifiable information from you. We do not oversee, nor can we be responsible for, these outside sources or their content. Be advised that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these extra-Site locations; we recommend that you take steps to understand how third parties will use your information before you agree to their terms of use.
In the event that we buy or sell a company, or one or more of our affiliated companies merges with or is acquired by another company, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the transaction. We may do this to ensure that services currently being provided to you may continue, or for other business purposes.
Our Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13. We hereby ask that individuals under the age of 13 not provide personal information through our Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without parental consent. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website to learn more about COPPA, or the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.
We employ all reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of data collected about you at our Site.
If you feel that this Site is not following its rules for data acquisition or use as stated in this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by mail, email, or telephone to resolve the matter. (Addresses and phone numbers appear at the bottom of this page.)
This Privacy Policy may change at any time; alterations will be indicated by a revised “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. Changes become effective when they are posted to the Site. Your use of the Site following any change indicates your unconditional acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy, so we encourage all users to periodically visit this page in order to view the most current version of these user terms.
In the event that you or those you represent do not agree to the use of your information as laid out in this Privacy Policy, you must cease your current use of this Site and not register for further use. If already registered, you must cancel your account and cease further use of this Site. Any continuation of use signifies your explicit agreement to be bound by and to comply with the terms laid out in this Privacy Policy; this agreement extends to any parties you might represent.
Mailing Address
The AAM Group
198 Industrial Park Road
Piney Flats, TN 37686
Email Address
sales@theaamgroup.com
Phone Number
(423) 282-0211
© 2020 AAM USA, Inc. All rights reserved.
